<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Amirmasoud</title>
    <link>https://example.org/categories/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Amirmasoud</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 03:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arlo / A hidden resturant in Salt Lake City</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2024/12/07/arlo-a-hidden-resturant-in-salt-lake-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2024/12/07/arlo-a-hidden-resturant-in-salt-lake-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a table reservation at 8 PM on Saturday at Arlo in Salt Lake City. It’s very close to the Utah State Capitol (&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Google Maps&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;), and it’s a bit hidden, though still quite busy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They have both indoor and outdoor seating, but it was too cold for me to sit outside. The indoor environment is beautiful and cozy, and the view of the quiet street on a Saturday was actually quite nice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving Dinner 2024</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2024/11/28/thanksgiving-dinner-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2024/11/28/thanksgiving-dinner-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the first time, I decided to cook a turkey for 2024 Thanksgiving! I’d never done it before, and I wasn’t sure what I needed, but I knew one thing for sure: I needed a turkey!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went to Costco and chose the smallest turkey they had, which was just over 10 pounds (sorry, little fella). They had turkeys over 20 pounds, but I went with the smaller size because it is just me (lol). The turkey was priced at $0.99 per pound. It was snowing in Salt Lake City when I went on Tuesday, November 26th. I grabbed my turkey, along with a couple of random seasonings, although I ended up not using them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STK / A fancy steakhouse in Salt Lake City</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2024/11/23/stk-a-fancy-steakhouse-in-salt-lake-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2024/11/23/stk-a-fancy-steakhouse-in-salt-lake-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to the STK steakhouse on Saturday, November 23rd, 2024. I had a table reservation for 8:30 PM. They offered me the choice of a dining table or a seat at the bar. I chose a dining table in the corner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At that time, the restaurant was fully packed with people dining. There was live music, and the lighting was dim. The server at my table brought me water and handed me the menu. They have a variety of foods and drinks to choose from, and, let’s be honest, they were pricey. Take a look at the menu:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aker / A resturant in Salt Lake City</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2024/11/16/aker-a-resturant-in-salt-lake-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2024/11/16/aker-a-resturant-in-salt-lake-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went there on Saturday night, November 16th, 2024, around 8:30 PM. I already had a table reserved for myself. I was warmly welcomed, didn’t need to wait, and was seated immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had checked their menu online beforehand and knew what I wanted to order, but I still reviewed their menu at the restaurant since prices weren’t listed online. Here’s their menu from their website:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
